<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="historic">Historic Places</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="golkonda">Golconda Fort</string>
    <string name="agolkonda">Khair Complex, Ibrahim Bagh, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="charminar">Charminar</string>
    <string name="acharminar">Char Kaman, Ghansi Bazaar, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="salar">Salar Jung Museum</string>
    <string name="asalar">Darulshifa Road, Near Minar Function Hall, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="makkah">Mecca Masjid</string>
    <string name="amakkah">Charminar, Ghansi Bazaar, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="chowmahalla">Chowmahalla Palace</string>
    <string name="achowmahalla">Motigalli, Khilwat, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="lumbini">Lumbini Park</string>
    <string name="alumbini"> Opposite Secretariat New Gate, Khairatabad, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="ntr">NTR Gardens</string>
    <string name="antr">NTR Marg, Central Secretariat, Khairatabad, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="jalavihar">JalaVihar</string>
    <string name="ajalavihar">Necklace Rd, Hussain Sagar, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="oceanpark">Ocean Park</string>
    <string name="aoceanpark"> Shankarpalli Road, Near CBIT College, Gandipet, Kokapet, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="zoo">Nehru Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="azoo">Bahadurpura, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="tajkrishna">Taj Krishna</string>
    <string name="atajkrishna">Rd Number 1, Mada Manzil, Banjara Hills, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="radisson">Radisson Blu</string>
    <string name="aradisson">Road Number 6, Banjara Hills, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="tajfalaknuma">Taj Falaknuma Palace</string>
    <string name="atajfalaknuma">Engine Bowli, Fatima Nagar, Falaknuma, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="novotel">Novotel</string>
    <string name="anovotel">Kavuri Hills, Kondapur, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="vivanta">Vivanta By Taj</string>
    <string name="avivanta">Begumpet, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="ramoji">Ramoji Film City</string>
    <string name="aramoji">Anaspur Village, Hayathnagar Mandal, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="wonderla">WonderLa</string>
    <string name="awonderla">Outer Ring Road, Exit No. 13, Ravirala, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="runway9">Runway 9</string>
    <string name="arunway9">Medchal Road, Kompally, Beside Mahindra Showroom, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="snowworld">Snow World</string>
    <string name="asnowworld"> Lower Tank Bund Road, Bharath Seva Ashram Marg,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="birlamandir">Birla Mandir</string>
    <string name="abirlamandir">Hill Fort Rd, Ambedkar Colony, Khairatabad, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="shilparamam">Shilpa Ramam</string>
    <string name="ashilparamam"> Hi Tech City Main Road, Madhapur, Near Cyber Towers, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="necklaceroad">Necklace Road</string>
    <string name="anecklaceroad">NTR Marg, Hussain Sagar, Khairatabad, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="d_image">d_image</string>
    <string name="d_title">d_title</string>
    <string name="d_desc">d_description</string>
    <string name="d_phone">d_phone</string>
    <string name="d_cost">d_price</string>
    <string name="d_time">d_time</string>
    <string name="d_address">d_address</string>
    <string name="d_url">d_url</string>
    <string name="d_latitude">d_latitude</string>
    <string name="d_longitude">d_longitude</string>
    <string name="de_golkonda">Golconda Fort is located in the western part of Hyderabad city and is about 9 km from the Hussain Sagar Lake. The outer fort occupies an area of three square kilometers, which is 4.8 kilometers in length.\nGolconda fort is undoubtedly one of most magnificent fortress complexes in India. The history of Golconda Fort goes back to early 13th century, when it was ruled by the Kakatiya’s followed by Qutub Shahi kings, who ruled the region in 16th and 17th century.\nThe fortress rests on a granite hill 120 meters high while huge crenellated ramparts surround this structure.</string>
    <string name="de_charminar">Charminar is a monument and a mosque, which is synonymous with the history of Hyderabad, India. The majestic structure was completed in 1591 CE and is not only a landmark building of Hyderabad but also a famous monument of India.\nA visit to Hyderabad is incomplete without visiting this grand and majestic centerpiece. It is also considered the Arc de Triomphe of the East. Some of the historians say that it was built it in honor of his wife, Bhagyamathi.\nThere is also legend that tells about the existence of a secret tunnel underneath the monument connecting the fort at Golconda that was created as a means of escape to royal family in an emergency. </string>
    <string name="de_salar">Located on the southern bank of the river Musi, Salar Jung Museum is popularly known for its one of largest one-man collections of the world. The museum is one of the Hyderabad sightseeing places that must be visited.\nSalar Jung Museum of Hyderabad is the third largest museum in India. It was declared open in the year of 1951 by the first prime minister of India, Jawaharlal Nehru.\nWith a collection of close to 43000 art objects, 9000 manuscripts and 47000 printed books, Salar Jung Museum promises a rich experience to all its visitors. The museum has 38 galleries which are spread in 2 floors. The ground floor of the museum is consisted of 20 galleries while the first floor has 18 galleries.</string>
    <string name="de_makkah">Mecca Masjid, also called Makkah Masjid, is one of the popular tourist spots of Hyderabad attracting not just devotees but almost everyone. The construction of Mecca Masjid Hyderabad involved close to 8000 masons who worked round the clock. This construction went on for almost 77 years.\nLocated in the Old City, at a distance of 100 metres from the Charminar which is another popular place for sightseeing in Hyderabad, Mecca Masjid is one of the largest mosques not just in India but also in the world.\nThe mosque has approximately 75-foot-high hall with dimensions of 220 feet by 180 feet. Interiors of the mosque are also beautifully decorated. It is believed that the main hall alone can accommodate 10,000 worshippers at a time.</string>
    <string name="de_chowmahalla">Grandeur of rulers, glory of its past, glimpse of their enigmatic way of living, are still alive in the form of palaces like Chowmahalla Palace, a place worth visiting when on a Hyderabad tour.\nBuilt in the 18th century, almost 200 years ago, the Chowmahalla Palace is one of the popular sightseeing places in Hyderabad. The literal meaning of this place is “Four Palaces” with “Chow” means four in Urdu and “Mahalat” which is the plural of “Mahalel” meaning palaces. Chowmahalla palace is said to resemble Shah Palace of Tehran in Iran.\nThe Chowmahalla Palace is consisted of two courtyards which are divided into the northern courtyard and the southern courtyard. The southern courtyard of the palace has four palaces which are namely Afzal Mahal, Tahniyat Mahal, Mahtab Mahal, and Aftab Mahal.Beautiful spread of lawn, its green landscape contrasting the yellow and white motifs of the palace presents a hypnotic sight.\nA huge water fountain in front of the palace, with artistically carved pillars is the first thing to offer a peek into the architectural excellence of this Chowmahalla palace.\nIntricate carvings on the walls and ceilings of the palace are also worth noticing. Glass chandeliers with different designs in each Mahal are also not to be missed.</string>
    <string name="de_lumbini">One of the famous Hyderabad tourist places, Lumbini Park Hyderabad was developed by the Hyderabad Urban Development Authority in the year of 1994. Perfect place for relaxation and amusement, Lumbini Park has been named after birthplace of Siddhartha who later came to be known as Lord Buddha.\nOne of the main attractions of the Lumbini Park is the giant clock at the entrance of the park which has been designed using various kinds of colourful flowering plants. Along with seasonal flowering plants, wide variety of cacti and rocks, the park also has many options to keep kids entertained.\nThe Musical fountain and water cascades attract everyone. The sight of water shooting up to the sky, making a screen of water where the history of Hyderabad is being shown is something not many of us have seen before. It is an experience in itself. The best part of laser show is that just 3D. You will see a city created in 3D right at a park.</string>
    <string name="de_ntr">Built in the memory of late Shri N T Rama Rao, former and one of the most popular chief ministers of Andhra Pradesh, NTR Memorial Gardens are one of the famous sightseeing places of Hyderabad.\nSpread across an area of 36 acres, NTR Gardens present a soothing atmosphere and refreshing setting to spend some time. The garden has been built with an approximate cost of Rs. 40 crore. It was in 2002, when the NTR garden of Hyderabad was opened to the public.\nThe Garden offers various kinds of recreational options as well. Some of these are boat ride, Japanese garden, Roaring Cascade, a Fountain, etc. There is a Children\'s playing area that keeps kids entertained.\nThe massive entrance plaza with Nandi Bulls is also quite captivating.A mini train on a single track takes the visitors all around the garden making your visit all the more enjoyable. Along with toy train, there is a wide array of recreational facilities at the NTR Garden. One of the latest additions to the NTR garden is the Desert Garden, brian child of Mr. Nitish Roy, who has designed this project. It is consisted of about 150 plant varieties, mainly of those plans which are commonly referred as desert plants such as cacti, succulents, etc.</string>
    <string name="de_jalavihar"> A popular amusement park, Jalavihar Hyderabad is situated on the Necklace Road which is in the heart of twin cities-Hyderabad and Secunderabad. It is quite close to the IMAX multiplex and Sanjeevaiah Park which is also on the Necklace Road. It is a family entertainment park with various interesting options for both adults and children.\nAn entertaining place to be with family, Jalavihar Water Park in Hyderabad, presents innumerable number of rides to its guests. There are wide range of water games as well as dry rides which are offered here, catering to both adults and kids.\nGames such as family slide, Mini aqua trailers, Tilt bucket, Mushroom Umbrella, Float slide and Pendulum are just a few of the choices that will keep you happy throughout your day at Jalavihar.</string>
    <string name="de_oceanpark">Situated at Gandipet which is 20 km from the city of Hyderabad, Ocean Park is an amusement park that promises each and every one a day full of entertainment and fun. One of the first theme parks that have been opened in the city, Ocean Park is spread across a huge area with two sections; one for water sports and another solely for amusement games.\nThis family amusement park, Ocean Park Hyderabad offers something for visitors of all age groups.\nThere are varied choices ranging from water rides, kiddies pool, wave pool, water slides and dry rides. Kiddies Pool, 60-Ft High Ride, the Slam Bomb and Bumping Cars are the major attraction of the Ocean Park. One can also go for Jet Skiing.\nDry rides such as Super loop, 60 feet high ride, bumping cars, slam bomb, Brake Dance, Super Jet and High Swinger promises at least a few moments filled with excitement and thrill. A wide range of water rides are Pendulum, Aqua Snake, Crazy Cruize, Zip Zap Zoom, Multilane Ride, Wave Pool, Harakiri,Tornodo, Aqua-Glide, Aqua Trail and Splash are also available.</string>
    <string name="de_zoo">Located at a distance of 16 km from Hyderabad, Nehru Zoological Park was opened to the public in the year of 1963. It is situated near the historically important Mir Alam Tank, which is 200 year old and is the first multi-arch masonry dam in the world. Nehru Zoological Park is one of the largest zoos of India and one of the top sightseeing places to visit in Hyderabad. Run by the Forest department, Government of Telangana, the zoo has been named after Jawaharlal Nehru, the first prime minister of the country.\nSpread over an area of approximately 380 acres, the Nehru Zoo Park boasts of almost 1,500 species of birds, mammals and reptiles. Adding to the extensive varieties of wildlife, this zoo park is considered to be the first one where animals have been kept in zoological order.\nAdding to the overall experience are the extensive range of activities to do in Hyderabad Zoo Park. Various Safaris, such as lion safari, bear safari and bison safari, along with toy train makes the visit all the more exciting. Butterfly Park, Jurassic Park, aquariums, etc., also let you explore the wildlife in a fun yet educational manner.</string>
    <string name="de_tajkrishna">With a history of over 100 years, Taj Krishna features a spa centre, a gym and an outdoor pool, amidst landscaped gardens. The hotel offers 5 dining options and shops.\nThe spacious rooms at the Krishna Taj hotel feature an elegant décor with dark wood, satellite TV and a minibar. Some rooms offer lake views.\nGuests can pamper themselves with a beauty treatment at Taj Krishna’s Jiva Spa, try a yoga session or work out with a personal trainer. Ticket service and baby-sitting are available.\nInternational food can be enjoyed at restaurant Encounters, while Firdaus offers Indian specialities and Golden Dragon serves Chinese dishes. Bar and Lounge Seasons offers live music and wines.\nHotel Taj Krishna is 30 km away from Rajiv Gandhi Hyderabad International Airport. It is 20 km from Hitec City.</string>
    <string name="de_radisson">Just 1 km from GVK One, Hyderabad’s largest shopping mall, the 5-star Radisson Blu Plaza Hotel boasts 3 dining options and an outdoor swimming pool. Guests enjoy free Wi-Fi and free parking.\nTastefully decorated, the luxurious rooms boast stylish modern interiors and large bay windows. They are well equipped with a flat-screen TV, cosy seating area and an en suite bathroom with a bathtub.\nRecreational choices include indulging in a relaxing body massage. Travel and sightseeing plans can be made at the tour desk.\nAvailable for all-day dining, Chill restaurant serves a spread of local and international dishes, while Pan-Asian cuisine is offered at the Holy Basil. For light snacks and refreshing beverages, guests can visit Bar 41.\nRadisson Blu Plaza is 2 km from Hyderabad Shopping Mall and 5 km from Hyderabad Railway Station. It is 9 km from Hussian Sagar Lake and 30 km from Rajiv Gandhi International Airport. </string>
    <string name="de_tajfalaknuma">Elevated 610 m above Hyderabad, this luxurious 5-star property features a blend of colonial and Indian designs. It houses a heritage walk with beautifully crafted objects from the world over and a first-rate spa.\nFeaturing high wood-beamed ceilings, these spacious rooms are furnished with pastel shades, floral fabrics and fine wood fittings. In-room comforts include down duvets and Egyptian cotton linen.\nLeisurely afternoons can be spent in the oak-panelled Palace Library or in the Billiards Room. Other features are a landscaped pool, fitness facilities and bespoke tailoring.\nTaj Falaknuma Palace is within 5 km of the beautiful Charminar monument and Chaumallah Palace. Offering free parking, it is about a 20-minute drive from Rajiv Gandhi International Airport and Banjara Hills.\nBoasting 6 dining options, highlights include afternoon tea in The Jade Room and relaxing sessions in the Hookah Lounge. There is also an Italian restaurant and poolside bar. </string>
    <string name="de_novotel">Connected to the Hyderabad International Convention Center, this 4-star hotel offers modern rooms with a bathtub and a flat-screen TV. Facilities include a spectacular outdoor pool, 2 restaurants and a bar.\nNovotel Hyderabad is a short drive from the Boulder Hills, an 18-hole champion golf course and several tennis courts. It is a 45-minute drive from Rajiv Gandhi International Airport. The hotel provides car and bicycle rental facilities for convenience.\nRooms are elegantly decorated and feature ample living space. They have satellite TV, a minibar, and tea and coffee making facilities. Some rooms offer nice views of the lake.\nThe Shahnaz Signature Salon and Spa offers a variety of health and beauty treatments, including 9 different relaxing body massages. The hotel also features a gym, a bike path, and a jogging track.\nThe Square at Novotel Hyderabad has 3 live cooking stations which serves local and international dishes. Guests can enjoy traditional Mexican food at La Cantina or dine in their rooms. </string>
    <string name="de_vivanta">This urban icon enjoys a central location between Hyderabad and Secunderabad, a short 3 km from Secundrabad Railway Station. Providing an outdoor pool, it also has a 24-hour fitness centre and free parking.\nThe modern air-conditioned rooms at Vivanta by Taj - Begumpet are equipped with a flat-screen TV, minibar and personal safe. Rooms enjoy views of the pool or city. En suite bathrooms come with a shower.\nVivanta by Taj - Begumpet is 5 km from Hyderabad Railway Station. Rajiv Gandhi International Airport at Shamshabad is 33 km away.\nInternational dishes and local delicacies can be enjoyed at Viva restaurant. Pan-Asian, Indian and continental cuisine, accompanied by exotic cocktails and martinis, are served at the edgy Tease lounge bar. Thai Pavilion, a Thai speciality restaurant offers a selection of fresh, distinct and well-seasoned soups, entrées, appetizers and desserts rooted in traditional Thai culture.\nCar rentals and day trips can be arranged at the tour desk. The hotel also provides a business centre and dry cleaning services.\nBegumpet is a great choice for travellers interested in friendly locals, shopping and food.</string>
    <string name="de_ramoji"> Located at a distance of 30 km from the city of Hyderabad, Ramoji Film City is on the NH-9. Built in the year of 1991, Ramoji Film City is one of the most popular sightseeing places of Hyderabad.\nOne of the largest and glamorous film studios in the world, Ramoji Film City has also place in the Guinness Book of World Records.\nSpread across an area of almost 2500 acres, it is one of the major film making facility of the country offering everything related to pre and post film production. The architecture of the studio and the wide range of settings makes it one of the favourite spot for many film makers.\nWith a capacity to accommodate close to 50 film units at the same time, Ramoji Film City offers umpteen numbers of film sets such as London Street, Hollywood sign, Japanese gardens, airport, hospital, etc. , landscapes and buildings as well as laboratories.</string>
    <string name="de_wonderla">Wonderla Amusement and Waterpark is undoubtedly a place of unlimited fun and boundless entertainment. Bestowed with Certificate of Excellence – 2015, Wonderla has been maintaining international standards of facilities along with an extensive array of dry and water rides and games.\nOne of the best entertainment parks not only in India but in Asia too, Wonderla Amusement and Waterpark is now opened in Hyderabad as well. Other two Wonderla parks are located in Bangalore and Kochi.\nWonderla Hyderabad Amusement and Water Park had been opened for public now, before than the previous estimation according to which this amusement park was to be functional and open to public by 2017.\nIt is now open, promising visitors with a range of thrilling rides and other entertaining activities. It is calculated that a cost of over 2.5 billion has been invested for the construction of this amusement park. It is located in Kongara Khurd A Village, Ravirala Post, Maheshwaram Mandal.\nAn amazing range of water rides, dry rides along with high thrill rides and dedicated rides for kids, keep every visitor happy and thrilled. There are around 43 thrilling rides to keep every visitor allured. Along with this, excellent dining choices and a wide array of facilities make the experience even better.</string>
    <string name="de_runway9">Go-karting is one of the sports and is increasingly gaining popularity amongst all age group. Hyderabad too has many places, offering its people the fun of Go karting. Runway 9 Hyderabad is family entertainment and adventure centre of Hyderabad attracting people of all age group.\nSaid to be the first and first and the largest Go-karting circuit in India, Runway 9 is place worth visiting. With a length of 711 meters which has been lit up using close to 50,000 watts of white metal halide lamps, it offers international standard of go karting. There are around 15 karts here. Jackets and helmets are offered at the centre itself. It is undeniably one of the best weekend places in Hyderabad.\nLocated at Kompally on Medchal road from Hyderabad, Runway 9 offers various kinds of entertaining facilities and not just go-karting. This is an ideal place to visit with friends or family. Even kids will love this place.</string>
    <string name="de_snowworld">Snow World has been recognized as the first snow-themed park of the country. OPML has also developed the Ocean Park Theme Resort of Hyderabad.\nSpread across an area of 17,000 square feet, Snow World is apparently the biggest snow themed park in the world. Situated at the Lower Tank Bund Road, behind the Indira Park, Snow World is one of the interesting tourist spots of Hyderabad. It is quite close to Hussain Sagar Lake as well.\nA perfect spot to beat the scorching heat of summer, Snow world has entertainment for each and everyone. There are various interesting options at the theme park to try on. Imagine throwing snow at each other without having to travel to any hill station. Snow world makes all this possible.</string>
    <string name="de_birlamandir">Birla Mandir in Hyderabad, dedicated to Lord Venkateshwara of Tirumala Tirupati Temple is said that a whopping quantity of white marble, which is almost 2000 tonnes, was brought from Rajasthan for building this temple. Located on the top of a hill of 280 feet, also known as Naubat Pahad, Birla Temple stands magnificently, drawing admiring glances from every passerby.\nThe architectural style of the Birla temple is a blend of North Indian and South Indian styles of temple architecture. The temple tower or the ‘Gopuram’ exhibits the salient features of South Indian temples. The Jagadananda Vimanam built atop the sanctum sanctorum resembles the Oriya style of temple architecture. It took 10 years of dedicated and hard work of sculptors and artisans to complete the construction of this temple.\nThe flagstaff of the Birla Mandir which has a height of 42 feet is made of brass. Scenes from the epics of Ramayana and Mahabharata are intricately carved on the walls and ceilings of the temple. The statues of deities belonging to Hindu mythology can be found from the entrance up to the sanctum sanctorum of the temple.</string>
    <string name="de_shilparamam">Located at a distance of 14 km from the heart of Hyderabad city, Shilparamam is a craft village which presents various traditional arts and crafts by artisans from all over the country. A perfect place for art lovers, Shilparamam is one of the popular tourist spots in Hyderabad.\nSpread across an area of 50 acres, Shilparamam not just showcases various artefacts and traditionally made handicrafts but is also a home for various performing artists.\nIn its complete form, the complex of Shilparamam is supposed to have Crafts Museum, Cultural Museum, Art Gallery and Library, Multi-purpose Auditorium, Common Facility Workshops and Research and Design Centre along with accommodation facilities for artists and visitors.\nThis is an ideal place for long walks too; its natural greenery dotted with carefully laid out sculptures and intricately designed buildings. There is also the facility of battery operated car which takes you for an enchanting tour of Shilparamam with a minimal charge.\nShilparamam shopping is the famous not just residents of Hyderabad but also among tourists.\nCraftsmen from all over India, display their works here, varying from traditional jewellery, hand-woven saris, shawls, dresses, bed sheets, etc; and hand-crafted wooden and metal wares. If you are looking for some street shopping, you have option for that too. There are many shops selling clothing of every kind in cheaper rates. All you require is some flair for bargaining.</string>
    <string name="de_necklaceroad">One of the prominent tourist spots of Hyderabad, Necklace Road presents a fun filled yet calm environment to spend some relaxed moments. Built in the same way as the Queen’s Necklace of Mumbai, the Necklace Road of Hyderabad also resembles a necklace.\nStretched across a length of three-kilometre, Necklace Road connects three major parks of the city, namely NTR Gardens, Lumbini Park and Sanjeevaiah Park. The road runs from NTR Gardens and Lumbini Park in Hyderabad to Sanjeevaiah Park in Secunderabad. And from Sanjeevaiah Park it runs to the Tank Bund Road which is later connected to the NTR Gardens. This gives it a shape of a necklace.\nThis place offers its visitors with various interesting options. One of the most popular of all is boating at the lake. There are two boarding points - one at Necklace road and another at Lumbini Park. The lighting show at the standing statue of Buddha in the middle of the Hussain Sagar Lake can be enjoyed while boating. The lighted Buddha statue and the view of lake, especially in night and early morning makes for an awesome photography venue too.</string>
    <string name="t_golkonda">9:00 A.M to 5:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_golkonda">Rs. 5.00 per person for Indians\nRs. 100 per person for Foreign Tourists\nRs.25 for Still Camera\nRs.130 for Sound and Light Show</string>
    <string name="p_golkonda">040-23512401</string>
    <string name="t_charminar">9:30 A.M to 5:30 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_charminar"> Rs.5 per Person for Indians\nRs.100 per Person for Foreign Nationals</string>
    <string name="p_charminar">040-66745986</string>
    <string name="t_salar">10:00 A.M to 5:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_salar">Rs.10 per Adult for Indians\nRs.5 per Child for Indians\nRs.150 per person for Foreign Tourists\nRs.50 for Still Camera</string>
    <string name="p_salar">040-24576443</string>
    <string name="c_makkah">No Entry Fee</string>
    <string name="t_makkah">4:00 A.M to 9:30 P.M</string>
    <string name="p_makkah">040-66745986</string>
    <string name="t_chowmahalla">10:00 A.M to 5:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_chowmahalla">Rs.80 per Adult for Indians\nRs.10 per Child for Indians\nRs.200 per person for Foreign Tourists\nRs.50 for Still Camera\nRs.200 for Video Camera</string>
    <string name="p_chowmahalla">040-24522032</string>
    <string name="t_lumbini">9:00 A.M to 9:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_lumbini">Rs.10 per person\nRs.50 per person for Speed Boating\nRs.40 per person for Boating\nRs.50 per person for Laser Show\nNA for Video Camera\nNA for Still / DSLR Camera</string>
    <string name="p_lumbini">9989336911</string>
    <string name="t_ntr">12:30 P.M to 9:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_ntr">Rs.15 per Adult\nRs.10 per Child\nRs.30 for Still Camera\nRs.65 for Camcorder</string>
    <string name="p_ntr">040-23450305</string>
    <string name="t_jalavihar">11:00 A.M to 7:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_jalavihar">Below 3 Feet Height Rs.150 Per Person\n3 Feet or Above 3 Feet Height Rs.250 Per Person\nDry Rides Cost: \nBungee Jump: Rs.50\nScary House: Rs.30\nCricket: Rs.30\nBouncy Castle: Rs.30\nWater garbing: Rs.50\nBull Ride: Rs.50\nBumper Car: Rs.50</string>
    <string name="p_jalavihar">040-20013106</string>
    <string name="t_ocean">11:00 A.M to 7:30 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_ocean">Rs.300 per Adult\nRs.230 per Child\nRs.250 per College Student\nRs.220 per School Student\nNA for Video Camera\nNA for Still / DSLR Camera</string>
    <string name="p_ocean">+9124193236</string>
    <string name="t_zoo">8:00 A.M to 5:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_zoo"> Rs.20 per Adult\nRs.15 per Child (below 12 yrs)\nStill Camera Charges:\nRs.20 for Still Camera (Amateur)\nRs.500 for Still Camera (Professional)\nVideo Camera Charges:\nRs.100 for Video Camera (Amateur)\nRs.500 for Video Camera (Professional)\nToy Train Charges:\nRs.15 per Adult\nRs.5 per Child (below 12 yrs)\nLion and Tiger Safari Fee:\nRs.40 per Adult\nRs.20 per Child (below 12 yrs)\nBuggy / Batter Operated Vehicle Fee:\nRs.50 per Adult\nRs.30 per Child (below 12 yrs)\nNocturnal Animal House Fee:\nRs.10 per Adult\nRs.5 per Child (below 12 yrs)\nFilm Shooting Fee:\nRs.8500 per Day Entry Fee for film shootings\nRs.1500 for Generator trucks for film shooting\nRs.1000 for Car/Jeep\nZoo Guest House Accomodation Fee:\nRs.500 for a family of 10 members\nOccupancy from 9 AM to 5:30 PM.</string>
    <string name="p_zoo">040-24477355</string>
    <string name="t_ramoji">9:00 A.M to 5:30 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_ramoji"> General Guided One Day Tour with-out-Food:\nAdult: Rs.1000\nChild (3-12 Yrs): Rs.900\nStar Experience One Day Tour with-Food:\nAdult: Rs.2099\nChild (3-12 Yrs): Rs.1899</string>
    <string name="p_ramoji">1800-42509999</string>
    <string name="t_wonderla">11:00 A.M to 6:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_wonderla">Adult: Rs.1,100\nChild: Rs.890\nCollege Students: Rs.940</string>
    <string name="p_wonderla">9100063636</string>
    <string name="t_runway9">2:30 P.M to 11:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_runway9">Rs.210 Go-Karting for 4 laps\nRs.270 Go-Karting for 6 laps\nRs.360 Go-Karting for 8 laps\nRs.450 Go-Karting for 12 laps\nRs.720 Go-Karting for 20 laps</string>
    <string name="p_runway9">040-27165642</string>
    <string name="t_snowworld">11:00 A.M to 9:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_snowworld">Rs.450 for Adult (4ft 6inch and above)\nRs.250 for Child (2ft to 4ft 6inch)\nRs.300 for College Students (above 10th Class)\nRs.250 for School Students (upto 10th Class)</string>
    <string name="p_snowworld">040-65990167</string>
    <string name="t_birlamandir">7:00 A.M to 12:00 P.M \n3:00 P.M to 9:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_birlamandir">Free</string>
    <string name="p_birlamandir">040-23233259</string>
    <string name="t_shilparamam">10:30 A.M to 8:30 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_shilparamam">Rs.40 per person for Adults\nRs.20 per person for Children\nRs.30 per person Boating charges\nRs.15 per person for Battery operated car</string>
    <string name="p_shilparamam">040-64518164</string>
    <string name="t_necklace">8:00 A.M to 10:30 P.M</string>
    <string name="c_necklace">Free</string>
    <string name="p_necklace">N/A</string>
    <string name="t_tajkrishna">Check-in: From 14:00 hours\nCheck-out: Until 12:00 hours</string>
    <string name="c_tajkrishna">Rs.6,500 avg. per night</string>
    <string name="p_tajkrishna">040-66662323</string>
    <string name="t_radisson">Check-in: From 15:00 hours\nCheck-out: Until 12:00 hours</string>
    <string name="c_radisson">Rs.5,440 avg. per night</string>
    <string name="p_radisson"> 040-49111133</string>
    <string name="t_tajfalknuma">Check-in: From 14:00 hours\nCheck-out: Until 12:00 hours</string>
    <string name="c_tajfalknuma">Rs.26,840 avg. per night</string>
    <string name="p_tajfalaknuma">040-66298585</string>
    <string name="t_novotel">Check-in: From 14:00 hours\nCheck-out: Until 12:00 hours</string>
    <string name="c_novotel">Rs.9,500 avg. per night</string>
    <string name="p_novotel">040-66824422</string>
    <string name="t_vivanta">Check-in: From 14:00 hours\nCheck-out: Until 12:00 hours</string>
    <string name="c_vivanta">Rs.7,500 avg. per night</string>
    <string name="p_vivanta">040-67252626</string>
    <string name="url_golkonda">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Golkonda</string>
    <string name="url_charminar">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charminar</string>
    <string name="url_salar">salarjungmuseum.in/home.php</string>
    <string name="url_makkah">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Makkah_Masjid,_Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="url_chowmahalla">chowmahalla.co.in/</string>
    <string name="url_lumbini">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lumbini_Park</string>
    <string name="url_ntr">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NTR_Gardens</string>
    <string name="url_jalavihar">jalavihar.in/</string>
    <string name="url_ocean">www.snowworldindia.net/oceanhome1.html</string>
    <string name="url_zoo">www.hydzoo.com/</string>
    <string name="url_tajkrishna">https://taj.tajhotels.com/en-in/taj-krishna-hyderabad/</string>
    <string name="url_radisson">https://www.radissonblu.com/en/hotel-hyderabad</string>
    <string name="url_tajfalaknuma">https://taj.tajhotels.com/en-in/taj-falaknuma-palace-hyderabad/</string>
    <string name="url_novotel">www.novotelhyderabad.com/</string>
    <string name="url_vivanta">https://vivanta.tajhotels.com/en-in/begumpet-hyderabad/</string>
    <string name="url_ramoji">ramojifilmcity.com/</string>
    <string name="url_wonderla">www.wonderla.com/hyderabad-park/</string>
    <string name="url_runway9">runway9.in/</string>
    <string name="url_snowworld">www.snowworldindia.net/</string>
    <string name="url_birlamandir">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birla_Mandir,_Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="url_shilparamam">https://www.shilparamam.in/</string>
    <string name="url_necklace">www.hyd.co.in/necklace-road/</string>
    <string name="open_details">Opening Details</string>
    <string name="open_website">Opening Website</string>
    <string name="open_map">Opening Map</string>

</resources>

